samsungapps.com 2010-05-28

# Samsung Apps

This Samsung Apps and Seller Office (“Website”) is operated by or on behalf of Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd, whose principal place of business is at 416 Maetan-3dong, Yeongtong-gu, Suwon-si, Gyeonggi-do, 443-742 Korea. This policy applies to information about you which is collected by us, by any company within the Samsung Electronics group of companies, or by any other company under the Samsung brand (“Samsung Group Companies”). A full list of Samsung Group Companies is available upon request. 

This policy sets out how we use and protect any information about you that you give to us through your use of the Website. If you have any questions or comments in relation to this policy, please contact our customer services department at the Help menu of the Website. 

We may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You are advised to check it from time to time in order to ensure that you are aware of any changes and that they are acceptable to you. This policy applies if you access the Website through your mobile phone, through your PC or through any other route. 

What information do we collect about you?

What do we do with your information?

How do we collect the information?

What about anonymous information?

To whom do we disclose your information?

Direct Marketing

Accessing your information

What do we do to keep your information secure?

Linking

Cookies and web beacons

What information do we collect about you?

  1. In general, you can view parts of the Website without giving us any information. On certain pages we will request information about you, for example, the registration pages. We will only be able to provide you with our full Website environment if you have completed and submitted the information required for the registration process and this is accepted by us in accordance with our Website terms and conditions. 

Some of the information that we collect will be ‘Personal Data.’ This means data related to you and which identifies you. In this policy, we use the terms ‘Personal Data’ and ‘information about you’ interchangeably. 

What do we do with your information?

  1. We may use information about you for any of the following purposes: 
    * to register you on our Website, to administer our Website services (including processing any searches or requests for information about our products or services), and to allow you to use those services (e.g. blogs, open forums and discussion pages); 
    * for assessment and analysis of our market, customers, products and services (including asking you for your opinions on our products and services and carrying out customer surveys); 
    * to enable us to monitor, review and improve the products and services which we offer; 
    * for internal record keeping; 
    * (subject to the direct marketing section below) for marketing purposes; 
    * to conduct free prize draws, prize competitions, or promotions; and 
    * to consider employing you if you have provided information pursuant to an application for a position with us. 
All of the above apply equally to the use of information about you for such purposes by a Samsung Group Company. 

How do we collect the information?

  1. We collect information about you using various methods, including: 
    * when you submit it through the Website; and 
    * when you telephone or email us, or correspond with us by means other than through this Website. 
We may combine information that we collect about you through this Website with information that you provide to us by other means, or that is provided to us by third parties. We may store that information together in a combined database or in separate databases. 

We will not retain information about you for longer than is necessary for the purpose for which it was intended, or as required under any contract or by law (and we will usually delete data once a user tells us that that he/she will no longer be using this service). We will not collect an excessive amount of information from you nor information that is not relevant to the purposes for it was collected. 

What about anonymous information?

  1. We may automatically collect technical information from which you cannot be identified when you connect to this Website. An example is the domain name of another website from which you linked to this Website. We collect this information to help us with identifying users’ browsing preferences. The information is used for internal purposes only so that we can carry out research on your demographics, behaviour and interests. Anonymous or generic information from which you cannot be personally identified is not Personal Data and is therefore outside the scope of this policy. 

To whom do we disclose your information?

  1. We will not disclose to any third parties Personal Data which relates to you without your consent, except: 
    * to a Samsung Group Company; 
    * where it is necessary to enable any of our staff, employees, agents, contractors, suppliers or commercial partners to provide a service to us or to perform a function on our behalf (including providing marketing assistance, market research or customer services; and administering your membership, supplying products or services that we provide to you now or in the future, or any free prize draws, prize competitions or promotions); 
    * to our professional advisers; 
    * to the purchaser or potential purchaser of our rights and obligations relating to this Website; or 
    * where it is necessary in order to pursue our legitimate interests or if we are required to or are permitted to do so by law. 
You acknowledge that any information that you submit into any environment that is visible to others (e.g. blogs, forums and discussion pages) will result in such information being published in like manner. You should take common sense precautions about the information you provide in such environments and acknowledge that your information will be published in such a way for others to see. 

For any disclosure of your Personal Data by us to a carefully selected third party or to any third party on the above list, we will comply with data protection law by ensuring that there are arrangements in place to ensure that the third party does not use your Personal Data for any purpose other than purposes that we specify and in accordance with the purposes outlined in this policy, and keep it secure. 

If we disclose your Personal Data to a Samsung Group Company or a third party which is outside the European Economic Area, we will not do so until we have taken steps to ensure that your Personal Data will be afforded the same level of protection as that required from us by data protection law. 

We will take all reasonable precautions to ensure that our staff and employees who have access to information about you have received adequate training to ensure that they process that information only in accordance with this policy and with our obligations under data protection law. We may take disciplinary action against our staff and employees in the event of non-compliance, should we consider this to be appropriate. 

Direct Marketing

  1. We may use information about you which we hold in order to provide you with information about products, promotions, and other such information which we believe may be of interest to you if you select to receive such information by email and/or post when you complete the registration process. 

You can change your mind about your preferences in respect of direct marketing by using the unsubscribe information on every such mailing or by updating your user profile. You can do this at any time. If you do so, we would not remove your Personal Data from our database(s) but we would note your changed preferences as soon as reasonably possible. 

Accessing your information

  1. Under certain data protection laws you may have the right to request details of Personal Data which we hold about you. If we are permitted by law, we may charge you a small fee. If you would like to make any such request please contact our customer services department at the Help menu of the Website. 

Please help us to ensure that the information about you that we hold is accurate and up to date. If you think that any information we have about you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to our customer services department in the manner set out above. We will correct or update any information about you as soon as reasonably possible. 

What do we do to keep your information secure?

  1. We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to do so, we have put in place reasonable procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect through the website. This has been done with a view to preventing unauthorised or unlawful processing of your Personal Data and accidental loss or destruction of, or damage to, your Personal Data. Whilst we have done all of this, we cannot guarantee that your information is secure when submitted or otherwise communicated through insecure means. 

We protect the security of your information by: 

    * using encryption where appropriate; 
    * using password protection where appropriate; and 
    * limiting access to your information (for example, only our staff or employees who need access to it for the purposes described above will have access to it). 
You must also take appropriate steps to keep your information secure by not using an obvious login name or password, by changing your password regularly, and ensuring that you do not divulge your password to any other person. 

Linking

  1. This Website may link to other websites which are outside our control. Whilst we try to ensure that we link only to websites that share our privacy and security standards, once you have left this Website we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide on other websites. You should exercise caution, and review the privacy statement applicable to the website in question. 

Cookies and web beacons

  1. We use cookies for certain areas of our Website. Cookies are files that store information on your hard drive or browser. They enable this Website to recognise that you have visited it before. Cookies help us to understand which sections of this Website are the most popular because they allow us to see which pages visitors are accessing and how much time they are spending on them. By studying these we are better able to adapt this Website to suit your demands and provide you with a more customised user experience. For example, cookies allow us to ensure that the information displayed on your next visit to this Website will match up with your user preferences. 

You may configure your browser to accept all cookies, reject all cookies, or notify you when a cookie is sent. Each browser is different, so check the "Help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences. For example, on Microsoft Internet Explorer, you can disable or delete cookies by selecting “Tools/Internet Options” and reviewing your privacy settings or selecting “delete cookies”. Please note, however, that this Website is designed to work using cookies and any disabling of them may affect your usage of this Website and prevent you from taking full advantage of it. We do not exchange cookies with any third party websites or external data suppliers, except with third parties working with us to provide services to you. 

This Website and the communications generated from using and/or registering on this Website, such as promotional emails, may contain electronic images known as "web beacons". Web beacons generally work in conjunction with cookies, and we may use them in the same way we use cookies (see above).
